because we seen a duplication of
organics you know versus in organics in
there that was a very interesting
question and I can't answer it without
telling a really different story
so I'm gonna have to pass on that when I
apologize so that's a short answer is
yes what's up the short answer is yes
probably yeah okay anybody from there
bleats Gelman yeah he wrote an
interesting little pamphlet it was
called animal vegetable and mineral life
and everybody thinks it's a typo because
it's animal life and vegetable life and
then we've got minerals but then I
started getting really deep into alchemy
I mean let me do mystify out to be
really quick alchemy is the study of
finding the seed of life of something
anything whether it be an element or
mineral whether it be gold or platinum
or whatever alchemy is discovering the
seed of life of something finding the
soil in which it's going to grow and
putting them together and cultivating
that so whether that means I'm going to
find the seed of life of gold and put it
together in the soil that it's going to
grow in let's say 10 and then
cultivating and letting it grow with
heat and multiplying my gold that's
that's one element of alchemy whether
that's an idea in a fertile mind and
putting it into and cultivating it with
proper thoughts proper energy and
directed action and creating a new
reality that's alchemy so what
Leedskalnin was talking about is saying
we're gonna find the seed of life of a
mineral we're gonna find it what it
grows in that's what the pamphlets about
he was talking about magnetic fields and
making it grow so and the pamphlet was
all about alchemy
most people think it's just kind of the
ramblings of a very eccentric person so
the short answer is yes the short answer
is we have seen organic life grow in
here how that is measured is a little
bit harder to quantify so that's that's
have we gone through all the materials
and the specs on the design are we ready
to talk about let me just show real
quick here this is a very I like this
way of putting power into it this is a
bolt or Samee this is a a pipe threaded
fitting through the wall of the of the
vessel and I put a bolt in here a
stainless steel bolt and welded it on
the end so that I get a completely
sealed completely sealed threaded
threaded insert with that I can put
electricity in and come out on the
inside so that's that's something that's
really important I struggled for a very
long time to figure out how to put an
electrode through with washers and and
such that aren't going to break down
over time and that are not going to not
going to suffer from the expansion and
contraction as this thing heats up and
cools off this is the best system that I
have found to do it the only the only
other system is to use that I like is to
use this as an electrode which I do on
the other which I do on the other on the
other machines but this is a this is a
little bit different way to do it so I
like this way you put a bolt through and
you weld it on and then thread that in
place and then you've got a contact
inside that you can run your run your
electricity off of and so this is just a
regular connection here just yeah this
is a this is a stainless steel bolt
let's run through and I just put on the
put on the wires with with two bolts and
tighten them down together the reason
why I put this glue in place there's
because I have experienced over time
these these bolts these nuts that have
been threaded onto the bolt over time as
they heat up and cool off they can
loosen up
you get a little tiny little tiny spark
in there and you got hydrogen right here
little tiny spark from the from the
contacts and boom so that's why I put
the the the glue in place there so that
that can't wiggle loose and and spark
what kind of glue that's once again the
the plumbing goop that's great stuff I
used to use that and that's what is
called commercial plumbing goop yes
that's what it's called okay plug it to
the purple it's in the purple purple -
what's up you can't use it for sealing
completely you cannot use it to just
seal the lid in place I've tried that
doesn't work you have to use the Teflon
you have to use something else something
to hold it pressurized like this holds
it together pressure holding it together
you cannot just use a solvent to hold it
unless you're using like like here this
is just solvent it on the pipe onto the
onto the lid or the cap rather but
that's four inches of solvent and it's
it's really strong so that's that that's
good but an inch of solvent or an inch
or so me having into solvent or half
ninja blue won't hold things together
you have to seal it with sealing with
compression what about these fittings
right here these are conventional C PVC
fittings you Biman at Walmart reversibly
home depot with teflon fittings I used I
use Teflon regular Teflon pipe tape to
thread that in place and there they have
a maximum their maximum heat is about
180 degrees but if you're running
hundred and eighty degrees here
something's wrong so you don't want to
go that high what about the fitting on
the bottom the fitting on the bottom is
just the same deal it's just gone out
sideways any reasons for the diameter
that you're using there it looks like
it's about a quarter-inch almost half
inch
yeah half-inch that I think these are I
think that's 3/4 inch NPT it's just
stuff I had laying around I could I
could use smaller I'll dispel it's not
really a myth but it's a it's a
conception that says you need huge pipe
or see these huge diameters
to run your gas through you can run 20
liters a minute through a through a
quarter inch pipe and I haven't seen any
significant drop or I haven't seen any
significant difference between using a
large pipe or a small pipe to run your
hydrogen through Saigon I don't think
you need a huge pipe in the beginning I
was using one inch diameter one inch
diameter hose to run my hydrogen to the
engines and such because I thought that
I needed to then I started doing some
experiments because that's you know kind
of what I was told so I started doing
some experiments and I've proved out
that I didn't need to I could use a
quarter or 3/8 inch diameter hose like
you see here and do it just fine so
what's up speck your graph I had a
friend who developed a detection
technology that is that is without par
okay it is amazing technology he had
even scan the moon okay he has
revolutionised shipwreck shipwreck
discoveries and get on the get on a boat
tune in for whatever he's looking for
whether it be gold or or jewels from a
Spanish galleon or something like that
and they could drive their boat to it
send divers down in there right on every
time so and it's a really beautiful
little of detection technology this is a
little device about gay big and they can
detect they can detect oh they detected
thorium obsess and cesium landing in the
mountains of Utah from Fukushima
divining-rod go home I don't think he
uses the vine crossing this Europe no
okay
so basically dialing any element on the
periodic chart give it to give it to the
the Police Department in Salt Lake City
they dial in the chemical compound of
methamphetamine drive to a meth lab so
they sent two of them to Iraq they're
not quite as user-friendly as the
military would like to have so they
they're not asking for more but
basically guys that were well trained on
him and we're very good with using them
could tell from a distance of five miles
where an improvised explosive device was
located they could tell the guys you
know forward three hundred yards and
you're gonna go to your right and you'll
find it they're very two feet
underground type of thing so the
technology is without five yeah it's
amazing stuff it's like having a
tricorder from Star Trek yeah I met
somebody down in the Mount Pleasant you
tire he who's passed away now who
developed a technology like that no I
can't remember his name
in my address book he passed away about
two years ago no yeah but anyway should
we talk now about the we've talked about
assembly and what's involved
what about operation how to run it
of course you put voltage in at some
point now what I believe from the
experiments and the and the things that
I've seen so far what I believe is that
a post frequency device will drop out
the elements that are there a DC device
will multiply the developments that are
that you've seen it with I could be
completely wrong on this and I'm
challenging people to try and figure out
you know the nature of this I mean here
we are Nikola Tesla we're going to throw
the AC motor out
and how many people can find new
applications for it here we are we've
got a hydrogen elements dropper outer
multiplier and go out and find out the
ramifications about it because this is
brand-new and anyone can do it I mean as
you can see it's not that it's not
difficult
you put voltage across and I just use I
just use a usually I used solar panel
sometimes welcome to my DC DC power
supply plug DC power into here and so I
can let it run for for a week straight
instead of you know on and off every day
and you get the same result it doesn't
care what these things come from here
okay the reason I ask that is because we
might think it's all the same by our
measurement detection but there could be
other things going on that we're not
aware of radiant energy flows over the
wires not through them for example
that's right and you want something to
flow you call a plumber not an
electrician energy flows around it not
through it you're absolutely right we
have actually discovered a distinct
difference between a solar panel voltage
and a lead-acid battery voltage and a
lithium-ion voltage don't ask me to
describe it it's it's it's a little bit
outside of you know where I'm
comfortable talking about because it
moves into the marriage of esoteric
energies and and science so it's very
interesting yeah very amazing roll and
call it against which one I am NOT a fan
of lithium-ion I do not like it I can go
into the environmental impacts of it you
can you you are less environments you
are less impacting the environment by
driving a Hummer that you are by driving
a Prius okay because of the lithium ion
and the
the environmental impact of making the
batteries and disposing of the battery
exposing of the batteries thank you yes
yes but just making them is incredibly
harmful the mining of the mining of it
the the manufacturing process the whole
thing but but we've you're replicating
it the minerals the lithium in the iron
using this then what well then then
we're looking at a complete we have the
ability now to to mine the ocean we have
the ability now to manufacture the
elements that we need all we need is
water and energy and a seed so the seed
of life finding where it will grow and
encouraging it to do so so perhaps then
things things will change but we don't
like the lithium ion there is a there's
aluminum in lithium-ion battery systems
this is going to get really esoteric so
if you guys don't like it on the video
that's for now but there was a woman
making the rounds in the prophecy club
about twenty years ago that could kill
rats using carbon dioxide gas killed
that should demonstrated as many times
on stage she could kill rats using
carbon dioxide gas lay her hands over
them and bring them back to life
many people witness best she's blessed
haven't brought it back to life
there's one criteria there could not be
any aluminum within 100 feet of where
she was working if there was she
couldn't bring him back to life one time
they thought they found all the aluminum
in the area that she was demonstrating
this and she was praying and they
weren't coming back to life which is
praying and blessing them and and they
found one little strip of aluminum on a
label underneath the table and she
grabbed the rats ran out into the field
knelt down and prayed over them they all
came back to life so I'm not a fan of
aluminum I'm not that crazy I'm not that
I'm not crazy but that intense about it
because
I'm not really rats back to life mine
aluminum when I did my research into the
Bible Code aluminum was one of the few
metals that had absolute injunctions
against using there were there were a
couple of the noble metals to actually
osmium was really bad and I want to say
it wasn't well go ahead I'm just gonna
ask what would be an aluminum substitute
since you're using aluminum in this
setting I keep oh I'm sorry
he wrote an interesting little pamphlet
it was called animal vegetable and
mineral life and everybody thinks it's a
typo because it's animal life and
vegetable life and then we've got
minerals but then I started getting
really deep into alchemy
I mean let me be mystify out to be
really quick alchemy is the study of
finding the seed of life of something
anything whether it be an element or
mineral whether it be gold or platinum
or whatever alchemy is discovering the
seed of life organic life grow in here
how that is measured is a little bit
harder to quantify so that's that's have
we gone through all the materials and
the specs on the design are we ready to
talk about
he's just show real quick here this is a
very I like this way of putting power
into it
this is a bolt or Samee this is a a pipe
threaded fitting through the wall of
something finding the soil in which it's
going to grow and putting them together
and cultivating them so whether that
means I'm going to find the seed of life
of gold and put it together in the soil
that it's going to grow in let's say Tim
and then cultivating and letting it grow
with heat and multiplying my gold that's
that's one element of alchemy whether
that's an idea in a fertile mind and
putting it into
and cultivating it with proper thoughts
proper energy and directed action we
seen the duplication of organics you
know versus in organics in there that
was a very interesting question and I
can't answer it without telling a really
different story so I'm gonna have to
pass on that when I apologize so that's
a short answer is yes
what's up the short answer is yes
probably yeah okay anybody from their
fleets Gelman yeah
and creating a new reality that's
alchemy so what Leedskalnin was talking
about is saying we're gonna find the
seed of life of a mineral we're gonna
find it when it grows in and that's what
the pamphlets about he was talking about
magnetic fields and making it grow so
and the pamphlet was all about alchemy
but most people think is just kind of
the ramblings of a very eccentric person
so the short answer is yes the short
answer is we have seen